I miss it so much. I haven't been here in a long time.
Secamin Cood.
Ouch ouch ouch ouch
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Huh? Huh?
Isn't it good?
Hello, I'm Yui Takemoto of Sakurazaka 46.
What a surprise!
Ta-da!
I'm here at the Kyoto Racecourse!
My grandfather used to be an education teacher.
I used to spend most of my weekends at Kyoto Race Track when I was a little girl.
Is that a bit of an exaggeration?
I'm not sure if that's a bit of an exaggeration, but the Kyoto Racecourse has recently undergone a complete renovation, and I'm very excited about it.
It has recently undergone a renovation.
I've always wanted to visit the track after it reopened, but I haven't had the chance to do so.
So I came here today because I wanted to enjoy Kyoto Racecourse for the first time in a long time.
I'm 21 years old now, and I'm old enough to buy a ticket.
I'm now 21 years old, which means I'm old enough to buy a ticket.
Today, for the first time in my life
I'd like to buy a ticket for the first time in my life.
Please do.
Come in.
On the left side, there's a new building that I'm not familiar with.
I've only seen the right side of the entrance.
It's been a long time since I've been here
Takehutoyo's chicken curry is on sale!
I've just entered the plaza from here, and here it is!
I'm going into the plaza from here, and basically the whole time...
I remember we used to come here in the morning and play all day long until the race came.
I used to fly on this dome so much.
I stepped into the nostalgic square.
We used to bring our leisure sheets and so on.
We all stayed here for a long time, didn't we?
The park is as big as ever.
It's still as big as ever.
I think it's the best playground.
Ever since I was a little girl.
I've always loved Mr. Turfy.
I wanted to take a picture of him
I always wanted to take a picture with him.
So my mission as a Takemoto girl at the racetrack was to look for Mr. Turphy
That was the mission of the Takemoto girl who came to the racetrack, wasn't it?
Sometimes Kitty was there, too.
There is a phantom three-shot of Mr. Turfy and Kitty.
She's probably about 2 years old
I wonder if I'll see Mr. Turfy today
We're walking here now, and it's like a plaza.
Everyone is eating and watching the race.
Originally, it was a paddock with a distant view.
It was originally a paddock in the distance, so it looks like a plaza with the paddock left as it was.
But for horse racing fans, it's like a dream come true.
It's like you're eating in the paddock.
I think it's like a dream come true for horse racing fans.
Maybe I'll come here again for a spot, alone.
Oh, isn't the race starting?
It's just starting.
Wow, I've been here many times.
Oh, it's started!
Wow!
Oh!
You're all running through here, each and every one of you.
Oh, my gosh.
I just tasted it.
Oh, my God.
I'm freaking out.
The rock race has started.
I need some Tarmac.
Wait, wait, wait.
I need a TURMING!
Mr. Tarming. - Hello, Mr. Tarming.
It's been a long time since I've seen Mr. Turbine.
It's been a long time.
Slow down.
Mr. Turbine.
I'll do my best. Last time I finished swinging.
I'm glad to see you. I haven't seen you in a long time.
A moving reunion.
May I have my picture taken with you?
You did it.
We did it!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Yeah! No!
Thank you!
Yeah!
I was really short when I was little.
I wish I'd been this tall, Mr. Turphy.
Yeah, sorry.
I was really about this height.
Mr. Turfy, you're always so kind to squat down for me.
You know, I'm the first person who's ever caught up to you in height, Mr. Tuffy.
Here we are in the paddock.
The new paddock.
It looks so different from the old one.
I've loved watching the paddock since I was a little girl.
I always came here to watch my grandpa's horse walk.
No matter how many times I see it, it's still exciting to see such a cool horse up close.
I still get excited no matter how many times I see it.
I just heard a halt.
I heard the horses stop once here.
And then the jockeys and the long-distance riders, I guess.
Then the jockeys and long-distance riders come to each horse.
At such times, I usually worked very hard.
I try my best to wave to the grandfathers and so on, but
but they don't always wave back.
The size of the water is really nice and easy to eat.
It looks so delicious!
It looks amazing!
You can see the horse's butt!
I just bought an awesome newspaper!
I'm going to predict the 10 Kyoto races now!
And listen up, everyone.
If you buy this...
I don't want any trouble with the staff.
I want the money I bought it with.
That's why I'm paying for it myself.
If I have to pay for it out of my own pocket...
I'll have to give up my New Year's gift to do it.
It's the first time I've ever predicted a race.
I've only ever watched horse races to see if Grandpa's horse would win.
I don't know how to make predictions, or how to change them.
I'm just trying it out for the first time.
Where should I start? But I don't have much time, and there's only 10 minutes left for the 10 races.
In race 10, the 6th horse is Ursus the Mountain Man, who has probably never lost a race before.
It's his fourth race, and he's finished first in all three.
He's a bad horse, you know.
And he's Mr. Manabu Yutaka.
He's by far the most popular horse in the race, and he's probably getting a multiple of one point.
I guess they're hoping he'll go for it.
But the second favorite, Miracle Tiara...
She's also very strong.
She's a horse that's only ever finished first or second.
So the knit here is really strong, maybe.
Maybe it's Miracle Tiara.
Meteorite, the fifth favorite.
I'm a little curious.
Miracle Tiara is the winner, and Yamaniurus and Meteorito are the secondary winners.
Okay, let's just do this one at a time.
I'm about to get cut off by the 10-horse team, so I'm going to run.
Where, where, where, where, where, where, where, where, where, where, where, where, where, where, where, where, where?
Where, where, where, where? Where, where, where, where, where, where, where!
- Pick an ordinance, too. Triple-cover 156, yes, Kyoto.
- Please also select electronic.
- Select electronic as well.
OK, here it is, here it is.
First time. My face fell a little bit.
For the first time.
- Thank you very much.
I bought it, I bought it, OK.
OK.
Um...
I'm safe now.
I bought a ticket.
Let's see, for the 10th race...
First of all...
I bought Miracle Tiara.
It was the second most popular horse.
It was probably 6.4 times the price.
Well, there is no doubt about it.
Miracle Tiara is definitely going to come.
I had a feeling that I wanted to bet on Miracle Tiara.
I bought 100 yen for a single win!
Here's the triplet.
I decided on the 156 trifecta.
My first ticket was like this.
These two tickets are 200 yen.
I'm looking at it here now.
Amazing!
Oh, no...
Yes, they're warming up.
The horses are warming up.
They're starting there. The horses are starting. That's where they're starting. They're getting close.
Come on!
They're starting!
What?
Miracle?
What's up?
Meteorito?
You didn't buy Meteorito?
You didn't buy a Meteorito?
I thought the Meteorito was nice, but... the third one is the third tiara, and the tiara is the third one.
The Miracle Tiara is the third tiara.
Miracle Tiara.
Miracle Tiara is number three.
Miracle Tiara is at the start.
Wait, what's number one?
Third.
Sixth, as I thought.
Sixth is strong.
Six is strong. Six is strong! Yes! I knew it? No, no, no!
Let the mountain hear you! Loud on the mountain!
I knew it! Strong! That's great!
Wow!
Wow! Wow, wow, wow.
Number two.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Oh, my God.
Let's go back one more time.
It's coming down the mountain.
Keep going.
He's been running since 2022 or something and he's never lost a race.
Are you kidding me? Really?
But I'm still very passionate about this race.
But I just want everyone to run safely, that's all I can think about.
Just like with Grandpa.
I'm so excited.
I'm going to predict the main race in Kyoto now.
Nikkei Shinshun Cup
Chi Chi
Rivian Glass looks awesome.
So that's how it is.
So that's what that was about.
So that's what the number 2 was about.
Well, Mr. Ikezoe, too...
Mr. Ikezoe, too.
All right...
Just in time.
Phew.
I called...
Single prize, number eight.
Blow the Horn, 400 yen.
And the second prize, No. 5 Red Valiente
500 yen.
I've already spent 500 yen on this Red Valiente.
And then 13 and 14 on the Umaren.
This is where Savona and Satono Glanz looked strong.
I bought 13 and 14 for 300 yen.
And the last trifecta is the second favorite.
I thought this Hearts Concerto was nice, too.
I'll take 5713 for 300 yen.
I'm going with 300 yen.
Go! Go!
Perfect fit!
Here we go.
They're taking out the new stations at 8, 5, 10, 3, 1410, cleanly down the middle, past the 4 between the 6 Miyazaki and the 4.
That number 1 minium wrasse.
In front of him is number 3 in 9th position.
He's now in 4th place.
He's now in 4th position.
Then, in front of number 3, number 23, Servonastown, on the drawer.
Oh, good, good, good.
Servona, good.
We've got 9 servos off the center of 8, less than 800, right there.
There's less than 800!
What?
Thirteen!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Six... six... six... six... six... six...
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Ow!
Oh!
Bro the phone, bro the phone, bro the phone, bro the phone
Bro the phone.
Seriously.
Wow!
Did you get it?
Birth Bro the phone.
What?
It's Bro the Horn.
I'll bet you $400 that you'll get a refund on that bro-the-horn you bought as a single bet.
You're married, aren't you?
Oh, my God.
Yay!
Four hundred and forty and six hundred and forty, yay!
Yay! It's my birthday!
400 yen became 1,640 yen!
Thank you! It's really like...
How much did I spend?
36...60 yen lost
I lost 60 yen.
I lost 60 yen... now let's get it back.
It's fun, isn't it?
Horse racing is fun.
This last one's going to be a strong one.
Second prize, number 5, Aroma de Rosa.
I won the second prize.
This is the second prize winner, Happy Awesome.
This one's also a very popular horse, number 10, and I was very aggressive.
I had a gut feeling that he would win.
I thought he'd tell me.
I bought Happy Awesome for the second prize.
And for the single prize, I bought
This one is also very aggressive.
Pilates, the third on the offensive card.
I got a little spooked at the Tadcock.
But that happens sometimes.
Aggressive ticket
It's starting to get bad!
And then there's the 710 on the horse train.
57 for the horse train
1510 for the trifecta.
OK.
Last race of the day.
I'm pretty happy with both the triplet and the triplet.
But I'm still missing 57.
I'm still missing 57, so I'm hoping he'll come.
He's in third place, fourth place.
Fourth, ninth, fifth, fifth...
Alma de Rosa is coming.
Pilates is the best.
Five, seven. Come on, five, seven.
Five.
Where?
Alma de Rosa?
Ten?
Seventy. Seventy.
What?
Wait, I don't understand. I don't know the order.
What? I don't know. I don't know the sequence.
I don't know what's impossible.
Wait, wait, wait.
The first, second, and third place winners were 1,15, and I bought 1,50 for the trifecta, so that's why I won the first prize, and...
And this number 5, Alma de Rosa, she's in the top three, so I won the second prize, too.
Okay, that's good.
Now we're back in it.
I'm going to refund you your winnings.
That's good.
But I'm just about even.
Or maybe it's exactly zero for me.
Thank you very much.
Oh, my God. You said 1,500 earlier.
That's 200.
Hmm?
How did this come up?
Oh, I guess you mean the one that came out here.
Is the refund correct? This one.
Oh, my God, is it right?
Well, I guess it's okay. There's a lot of them.
All the races in Kyoto have already been completed.
I ended up buying tickets for 3 races, Kyoto 10, 11, and 12.
Overall, I was able to finish with a little bit of money in my pocket.
It was the first time in my life to think about which horse would come in.
It was the first time in my life to think about which horse would come in and to buy a ticket for a horse.
It was a lot of fun!
I hope you'll join me again in the future!
What's that beeping?
Race 12 in Nakayama has just started.
I'm going to talk about race 12 in Nakayama at the end.
I'm going to enjoy horse racing more and more from here.
I'd like to enjoy horse racing more and more from here.
I'd like to enjoy horse racing as much as I can from here.
I hope all of you Buddies will join me in enjoying horse racing.
If you are interested in horse racing, please leave a comment or give me a high rating and a good button.
If you are interested in horse racing, please leave a comment or give me a high rating and a good button!
I'll do my best for the second installment!
Here's the Nakayama Juniors!
Bye bye!
bye-bye!